(Various:)Hi, Stuart.
(Stuart:)Oh, good, I'm glad you guys
didn't wait for me to start.
Although you said 7:00
and it's 7:00. That's fine.
(Amy(ringing from tablet):)Oh, it's probably Sheldon.
(Amy(ringing from tablet):)Hi, Sheldon.
(Amy(ringing from tablet):)Everybody's here, say hi.
(Penny:)-Hi.
-Hey, buddy.
(Penny:)Hey.
(Howard:)-Howdy.
-Hi.
(Stuart:)Hello.
(Sheldon:)The second
I go out of town
(Sheldon:)you throw a Christmas
party without me?
Yeah, kind of.
(Sheldon:)That's so thoughtful.
You guys are the best.
(Penny:)Hey, how's your sister?
(Sheldon:)She went into labor an hour ago.
(Amy:)That's wonderful.
So you're at the hospital?
(Sheldon:)No, she chose to have a home
birth, because she wants
(Sheldon:)to live in the Stone Age
and a cave wasn't available.
(Raj:)You know, many people believe
(Raj:)that home births are better
because the mother
(Raj:)is in a warm, comfortable environment
(Raj:)where she can be
nurtured by loved ones.
(Sheldon:)And turn the bedroom floor
into an amniotic Slip 'n Slide.